phixr.com 2018-08-30

# Phixr - Online Photo Editor [Legal]

Phixr Terms of Use

By using any of the Phixr websites (hereinafter "the Site") you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions ("Terms of Use"):

  * The Site is intended exclusively for personal use and is not a generic data hosting service.
  * You may not use the Site's service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. Users agree to comply with all applicable local laws regarding online conduct and acceptable content.
  * You must not, in the use of the Site, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws).
  * You must not create or submit unwanted email to anyone ("spam").
  * You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.
  * You are responsible for any activity that occurs under your user name.
  * You are responsible for keeping your password secure and secret. Making your account data public will lead to account termination.
  * You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, information, user names, files, links ("Content") that you submit and post on the Site.
  * You must not modify, adapt or hack the Site or modify another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with the Site.

Violation of any of these terms will result in the termination of your account.

General Conditions

  * We do not claim, nor gain any right with regard to data you upload to our servers. It's your data, and it remains your data.
  * We reserve the right to modify or terminate the free service the Site provides for any reason, without notice at any time.
  * We reserve the right to alter these Terms of Use at any time. If the alterations constitute a material change to the Terms of Use, we will notify you via e-mail if you specified an e-mail address in your profile. What constitutes a "material change" will be determined at our sole discretion, in good faith and using common sense and reasonable judgement.
  * We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.
  * We may, but have no obligation to, remove Content and accounts containing Content that we determine in our sole discretion as unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party's intellectual property or these Terms of Use.

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information of our users.

What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This privacy policy pertains to the use of the Site at http://www.phixr.com/ and related or affiliate sites in different languages.
  * This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we eventually collect and receive. Personal information - in general - is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, email address, or phone number if applicable.

General Information

  * We do not request any data that is personal when registering with the Site.
  * The Site automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the page you request.
  * We use this information for the following general purposes: product and service provision, identification and authentication, service improvement, research, and anonymous reporting.

IP Addresses

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. We do not store your IP address anywhere, except in server logs (see above). These logs are deleted within 7 days.

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address.
  * To estimate the total number of users visiting the Site from specific geographical regions.

e-mail

An e-mail address is not a requirement for using the site. It is only required if the user wants to e-mail photos directly from the Site. In that case, the provided e-mail address will be verified and only used as a sender address when the user e-mails photos from within the Site. The provided address can be removed at any time using the Settings page.

Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

  * You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.
  * If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use the Site.
  * The Site uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to 
    * access your information when you sign in (regardless whether for a temporary session as a guest or by using your registered account details),
    * keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the Site's services,
    * display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on the Site,
    * estimate and report our total audience size and traffic,
    * conduct research to improve the Site's content and services.
  * The Site lets other companies [that show advertisements on some of our pages, or perform user counting, eg. Google] set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to the Site's own cookies.
  * This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ('Google'). Google Analytics uses 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. _Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google._ You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you will not be able to use this website. By accepting these terms and conditions, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. _This website runs Google Analytics with the extension "_anonymizeIp ()" to truncate IP addresses in order to avoid a direct link to individuals and provide full anonymity. If your browser sends a "Do not track"-header, tracking is disabled._ For further information, please see [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners?hl=en)

Even more information on cookies is here. 

Facebook permissions

For Phixr to provide all its Facebook-related services, it needs certain permissions to access your Facebook data. Here is which permissions are needed and what Phixr uses them for:

  * **"Your basic info"** : Phixr only uses _your name_ for tagging yourself in a photo, and the _list of your friends_ for tagging them and accessing their photos. No other information is accessed or used.
  * **"Your Photos" and "Photos shared with you"** : This is for allowing Phixr to _download your photos_ from Facebook, including photo tags.
  * **"Post on your behalf"** : As dangerous as this might sound, in fact, this is only needed to _upload photos_ to your albums. Phixr does not "post" anything to your wall. As of August 2013, this permission is not asked for upon entering Phixr, only later if you want to upload a photo.
  * No data obtained from Facebook is stored in Phixr longer than needed to provide named features. All such data is deleted within a maxium of 120 minutes after the last access.

You can revoke all permissions from within the "Privacy" page in your Facebook account settings. If you remove Phixr as a Facebook app, permissions are revoked and Facebook notifies Phixr; in that case Phixr will permanently delete all your Facebook related data.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * When you e-mail a photo, your Site user name that you are registered under is visible to the recipient(s) of the e-mail. So is the e-mail address you specified in your profile.
  * We do not rent or sell or share any personal information.
  * It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Site's Terms of Use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. We will transfer information about you if the Site or our company is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. We may share demographic information with business partners, such as "12% of users who regularly use the Site are from countries that start with 'A'" or the like. No personally identifiable information will ever be used without your permission.
  * The Site displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. For further information, please see [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners?hl=en)
  * All personal information and other data will be stored and processed in the United States and this information may be subject to the laws of this jurisdiction.

Editing Account Information. Security.

  * You can change your Account Information, at any time.
  * We may send you certain communications relating to the Site's service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your account.
  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * Your Account Information is password-protected.
  * In certain areas, the Site may use SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

How to contact us

e-mail: 

Trademarks and Acknowledgements

Phixr and the Phixr logo are protected trademarks. No material from this site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way without his prior written consent.

Facebook and the Facebook logo are (registered) trademarks of Facebook. Used by permission (in accordance to the general permission stated [here](http://developers.facebook.com/documentation.php?doc=login_web) and to Section 6 of Facebook's "Developer Terms of Service" dated July 25, 2007).  
Flickr and the flickr logo are (registered) trademarks of Yahoo! Inc. Used by express permission.  
  
LiveJournal and the Livejournal logo are (registered) trademarks of LiveJournal, Inc. Used by express permission.  
Photobucket and the photobucket logo are (registered) trademarks of Photobucket, Inc. Used by express permission.  
Picasa and the Picasa logo are (registered) trademarks of Google Inc. Used by permission.  
SmugMug and the SmugMug logo are (registered) trademarks of SmugMug, Inc. Used by express permission.  
Twitter and the Twitter logo are (registered) trademarks of Twitter, Inc. Used by express permission.  

This product uses the Flickr API and other APIs, but is not endorsed or certified by Flickr and/or Yahoo! Inc and/or any other of the companies named above.

This product makes use of algorithms described in: "Fast Anisotropic Smoothing of Multi-Valued Images using Curvature-Preserving PDE's." (D. Tschumperle), International Journal of Computer Vision, IJCV(68), No. 1, June 2006, pp. 65-82.

Products and company names are being used without references to trademarks, patents or copyrights. Therefore, the lack of a respective notice does not permit the assumption that a name is free of rights.

Effective Date: April 12, 2018.
